

## NILOOFAR BIGDELI

### **Social Media Specialist**

- +46 722-584-687
- In /niloofar-bigdeli
- bigdeli.niloofar1992@gmail.com
- ⊕ Portfolio

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Social media tools:
   LinkedIn Ads | Facebook
   Business Suite | Hootsuite |
   Sprout Social
- Digital marketing tools:
   Google Analytics 4 | Google
   Tag Manager | SEO | HubSpot
- Content creation tools:
   Adobe Photoshop | Adobe
   After Effects | Adobe
   Premiere | Canva
- UX/UI design: Adobe XD |HTML | CSS

#### **PROFILE**

As a seasoned digital marketer with a focus on social media and content creation, I bring more three years of experience in the digital marketing realm. Currently, I am exploring opportunities within Sweden's digital marketing landscape, aiming to utilize my skills to drive impactful outcomes and appealing content.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



- Digital Marketing Specialist
   11/2023 Present | PiipII
  - Delivering monthly content kits for consistent, engaging posts on multiple platforms.
  - Creating visual content for Instagram, LinkedIn, and TikTok.
  - Analyzing post-performance to optimize future content strategies.
  - Engaging in paid social to increase brand visibility.
  - Creating strategies to effectively grow and engage the community.

### Social Media Specialist 04/2021 - 10/2022 | Loop54 (FactFinder)

- Managed company SoMe accounts on <u>LinkedIn</u>, <u>Twitter</u>, and <u>Facebook</u>, overseeing content strategy and execution.
- Provided monthly content kits, ensuring consistent and engaging posts across platforms.
- Analyzed posts' performance, leveraging data to optimize future content strategies.
- Cross-functional collaboration on SoMe campaigns, resulting in a >2x increase in CTR and a 20% decrease in CPC compared to previous campaigns.
- Achieved significant improvements in KPIs within one year, including a remarkable 114% increase in engagement, and 72% boost in impressions.

# Social Media Marketing Specialist 11/2018 - 03/2019 | Inverse Digital School

- Social Media Manager with a primary focus on <a href="Instagram">Instagram</a> and <a href="YouTube">YouTube</a> platforms.
- Developed and executed the monthly social media strategy, planning and creating appealing content to boost engagement and enhance brand visibility.
- Implemented effective micro-influencer marketing campaigns, driving a notable increase in website visits and expanding the company's online presence.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Digital Marketing Specialist**

2023 | Sälj & Marknadshögskolan | Sweden

### Executive Master of Business Administration

2016 – 2018 | Allameh Tabataba'i University | Tehran, Iran

# Bachelor of science in Management

2011 - 2015 | Payame Noor University | Tehran, Iran

### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Digital Fluency
Collaborative Team Player
Positive and adaptive thinking
Attention to Detail
Cross-Cultural Competence

#### **LANGUAGE**

English - Professional working proficiency

Swedish - Basic knowledge

Persian - Native

### Digital Account Manager

02/2017 - 09/2018 | Boomrang Digital Marketing Agency

- Overseeing the social media presence of multiple companies (e.g., <u>Sunich</u>, <u>Castrol</u>), each with unique objectives with a focus on Instagram.
- Developed content plans tailored to each company's specific goals.
- Facilitated communication with content creators to maintain high-quality content.
- Effectively supervised communication with users, fostering positive interactions and brand loyalty.

#### **CERTIFICATES**



- ChatGPT Prompt Engineering
- Foundations of Digital Marketing and Ecommerce
- The Ultimate SEO Training + SEO For WordPress Websites
- **♦** Master Google Analytics 4 and GTM basicss
- **■** Marketing with TikTok

# OTHER RELEVANT EXPERIENCE



### Event Manager

Boomrang digital marketing agency

- Managed and coordinated multiple marketing events, strategically inviting loyal customers of our clients as well as social media influencers.
- Designed engaging games and entertainment activities, aiming to enhance our clients' social media presence and foster stronger connections with customers.

### Business Development Manager Banowin

 Co-founded an eCommerce startup called Banowin with a mission to empower women in Iran who were unable to work in traditional social roles by providing a platform to sell their handmade products or food online.

